thestayathomechef.com 2019-12-07

# Policies - thestayathomechef.com

The Stay At Home Chef is a property of Farnsworth Media LLC  
 ** _  
_**  
 ** _Content Use Policy_**

Before using any content from this blog, including pictures or recipes, please contact me for permission at stayathomechefblog at gmail dot com. All work is copyright of Rachel Farnsworth and The Stay At Home Chef. Any use of material without written consent is prohibited.

 ** _Advertising Affiliates_**

The Stay At Home Chef is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com.

The Stay At Home Chef is a participant in other affiliate programs including Commission Junction and ShareASale. I receive a portion of any purchases made on these sites after clicking on these links. 

**_Disclosure Policy_**

This blog is a personal blog written and edited by me. For questions about this blog, please contact [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content.

The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

This blog does contain content which might present a conflict of interest. This content will always be identified.

 ** _Privacy Policy_**

Privacy Policy for www.thestayathomechef.com

The privacy of our visitors to www.thestayathomechef.com is important to us. At www.thestayathomechef.com  we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit www.thestayathomechef.com  and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Log Files  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on www.thestayathomechef.com to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

### Get New Recipes Sent To Your Inbox ?

Join my newsletter and get new mouth watering recipes sent directly to you weekly!
